http://moneymanagement.org/about/security/privacy

Skip to Content
I need help...
Credit Card Debt
Fortunately we can help take away the pain and uncertainty of overwhelming debt.
Learn More
I want to learn how to...
How to Earn Extra Money in the Gig Economy
Find a side hustle and boost your income.
Read More
Find inspiration in their stories
A college professor overcomes years of credit card debt
A retired couple avoids losing their home after a pair of unexpected setbacks
A retiree escapes 50 years of debt
A hardworking single mom finds the key to stabilizing her finances
A couple save themselves after years of financial mismanagement
Featured Blog Post
Best Apps for Finding Side Gigs and Earning Cash
Need to balance your budget with some extra income? These side hustle apps are a great place to start looking.
Careers at MMI
At MMI, we strive to change how America overcomes financial challenges; one person, one experience, one solution at a time.
Debt Management Plans
Consolidation without a loan. Discover the benefits of this budget-friendly debt repayment option.
MMI and the Military
See how MMI helps military service members and their families reconnect and find financial security.
A college professor overcomes years of credit card debt
A retired couple avoids losing their home after a pair of unexpected setbacks
A retiree escapes 50 years of debt
A hardworking single mom finds the key to stabilizing her finances
A couple save themselves after years of financial mismanagement
Internet Privacy & Usage Agreement
We understand the importance and value of your privacy. That’s why we strive to be transparent about how your interactions with online MMI properties, including its website and app, are monitored and what happens to any information that you choose to share with us.
Information is not transferred to any third parties unless you ask us to. This means that the security of any personal information shared is solely protected by MMI.
Only authorized staff members have access to specific areas of consumer information. MMI follows strict guidelines to limit and protect access to client information.
Visit our security section to learn more about the steps we take to protect your sensitive information.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
Click here for a PDF version of our Internet Privacy and Usage Policy
We do not collect personal information, such as your name, address, phone number, or email address, while you browse MoneyManagement.org or any other MMI-operated online properties. We do, however, gather information on how our online properties are used, such as the number of visitors, length of each visit, and which pages are most commonly used to enter and exit each website or app.
Some areas of MMI online properties utilize tools, including browser cookies, in order to enhance the client experience. You have the option of disabling cookies in your browser if that is your preference.
Many sections on the MMI website are provided for the benefit of the consuming public. You may request consumer educational information or other services in these sections. In order for us to fulfill your request, you may need to provide us with your email address, regular mail address, or telephone number. Our use of that information will be as described on those pages.
Should you choose to seek financial counseling from MMI, you may voluntarily complete all or a portion of our online counseling form. Several types of personal information may be gathered through this form for use in your confidential counseling session, including name, address, telephone number, social security number, employment information, and creditor information, including account numbers. Specific uses of this information may be to:
Identify your accounts with your creditors
Contact you and to confirm your identity when you call us
Contact and negotiate with your creditors
Demographic data may also be used for statistical studies, though names are not used without specific permission.
MMI does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected through this or any other online property. All personal information is used solely by MMI, with consumer consent.
As part of an effort to improve advertising quality, MMI online properties may allow Google to detect a short segment of text (known as a cookie) that Google previously placed on your computer. No personal information (e.g. your name or contact information) is included in the cookie that Google detects. For more information about Google and privacy, please read Google's Privacy Policy.
Downloads
Money Management International cannot and does not guarantee or warrant that files available for downloading through MMI's online properties will be free of infection, viruses, worms, or other code that manifest contaminating or destructive qualities. You assume total responsibility and risk for your use of any apps, websites, and the Internet.
Data Quality
All information submitted to MMI is transmitted via industry standard methods of data collection and transmittal. Our data storage devices are designed to accurately and safely store your data, thereby substantially minimizing the possibility of data corruption. If for any reason, you need to contact MMI for the purpose of correcting inaccurate data transmittal, contact us at esupport@moneymanagement.org.
State Guidelines
For MD Residents Only: The Commissioner of Financial Regulation for the State of Maryland will accept any questions and complaints from Maryland residents regarding Money Management International, Inc. (license #14-13) at 500 N. Calvert St., Suite 402, Baltimore, MD 21202. Phone: 1-888-784-0136.
Agreement
By using our online properties, you agree to MMI's Internet Privacy and Usage Policy and to the use of the information we receive and collect as stated herein and in ways we may notify you of in the future. By providing any personal information, you acknowledge that you fully understand and consent to the collection and processing of such information. We reserve the right at our discretion to modify this Internet Privacy and Usage Policy at any time. Your continued use of MMI online properties following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.
About MMI
Our History
Mergers
Our Story
Guiding Principles
Mission and Vision
Leadership
Jim Triggs
Consumer Federation of America
The Consumer Federation of America (CFA) is an association of nonprofit consumer organizations that was established in 1968 to advance the consumer interest through research, advocacy, and education. Today, nearly 300 of these groups participate in the federation and govern it through their representatives on the organization's Board of Directors.
Homeownership Preservation Foundation
Since 2007, the Homeownership Preservation Foundation (HPF) has served as a trusted, neutral source of information for more than eight million homeowners. They are partnered with, and endorsed by, numerous major government agencies, including the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development and the Department of the Treasury.
Department of Housing and Urban Development
The mission of the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) is to create strong, sustainable, inclusive communities and quality affordable homes for all. HUD works to strengthen the housing market in order to bolster the economy and protect consumers; meet the need for quality affordable rental homes; utilize housing as a platform for improving quality of life; and build inclusive and sustainable communities free from discrimination.
Council On Accreditation
The Council on Accreditation (COA) is an international, independent, nonprofit, human service accrediting organization. Their mission is to partner with human service organizations worldwide to improve service delivery outcomes by developing, applying, and promoting accreditation standards.
National Foundation for Credit Counseling
The National Foundation for Credit Counseling® (NFCC®), founded in 1951, is the nation’s largest and longest-serving nonprofit financial counseling organization. The NFCC’s mission is to promote the national agenda for financially responsible behavior, and build capacity for its members to deliver the highest-quality financial education and counseling services.
×
Visit (Partner URL)
×
×
Session Timeout
Your session will expire in
